Austria
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Austria
2.1.1.1.1
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1173
- Austria, 2.1.1.1.1
  - The old fortress, Kufstein, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 1; 11000; 5x7 (Box 1173)
  - Old fortress on a rock, Kufstein, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 2; 11002; 5x7 (Box 1173)
  - The valley of the Inn, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 3; 11004; 687; 5x7 (Box 1173)
  - Narrow street, Hall, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 4; 11010; 5x7 (Box 1173)
  - Street in Hall, Ehn Valley, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 5; 11012; 5x7 (Box 1173)
  - Marie-Thereseien Strasse, looking toward the Anna Saule, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 6; 11013; 5x7 (Box 1173)
  - Marie-Theresein Strasse showing style of architecture, Innsbruck, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 7; 11014; 5x7 (Box 1173)
  - Looking down Marie-Theresien Strasse toward the mountain, Innsbruck, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 8; 11019; 5x7 (Box 1173)
  - Looking down Herzog-Friedrich Strasse, Innsbruck, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 9; 11020; 5x7 (Box 1173)
  - Golden Adler Hotel in the Herzog-Friedrich Strasse, Innsbruck, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 10; 11021; 5x7 (Box 1173)
  - Golden Adler Hotel, Innsbruck, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 11; 11022; 5x7 (Box 1173)
  - Balin Strasse[?] near the railway station, Innsbruck, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 12; 11033; 5x7 (Box 1173)
  - Old castle just outside of Innsbruck, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 13; 11045; 5x7 (Box 1173)
  - Armor of King Theodorich, Innsbruck, before 1916; 14; 4x5 (Box 1173)
  - Innsbruck von Berg Isel, Austrian Tyrol, copy, before 1916; 15; 4x5 (Box 1173)
  - Innsbruck von der Weiherburg, copy, 1910 July; 16; 4x5 (Box 1173)
  - Modern castle in the Bremer Pass, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 17; 11046; 5x7 (Box 1173)
  - View on road just south of Innsbruck, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 18; 11047; 5x7 (Box 1173)
  - In the Val Ampezzo, Dolomites, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 19; 11062; 5x7 (Box 1173)
  - Frank R. Roberson and Mrs. Jessie W. Roberson in automobile in Ampezzo Valley, Dolomites, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 20; 11063; 752; 5x7 (Box 1173)
  - The Campanile, Cortina d' Ampezzo, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 21; 11067; 5x7 (Box 1173)
  - Fields of flowers, mountains, before 1916; 22; 11082; 5x7 (Box 1173)
  - Garden, before 1916; 23; 11095; 792; 5x7 (Box 1173)
  - House, many pictures on wall, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 24; 4x5 (Box 1173)
  - Street scene, Innsbruck, Austrian Tyrol, before 1916; 25; 5x7 (Box 1173)
  - Men climbing, Schneerinne, copy, before 1916; 26; 4x5 (Box 1173)
  - Mittenwald, copy, 1910 July; 27; 4x5 (Box 1173)
  - Dolomitenst, copy, 1910 July; 28; 4x5 (Box 1173)
  - Lermoos, mountains in distance, copy, 1910 July; 29; 4x5 (Box 1173)
  - Town and mountains, Lofer, Copy, 1910 July; 30; 4x5 (Box 1173)
  - Ornate building, Austria, Copy, before 1916; 31; 4x5 (Box 1173)
  - Man, Austrian Tyrol, Copy, 1910 July; 32; 4x5 (Box 1173)
  - Woman, Austrian Tyrol, Copy, 1910 July; 33; 4x5 (Box 1173)
  - Andreas Hofer, Copy, 1910 July; 34; 4x5 (Box 1173)
  - Hans Makart, Copy, 1910 July; 35; 4x5 (Box 1173)